question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The first computer bug was formed by faulty wires.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; "
                    "was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Pablo Picasso is one of the founding fathers of &quot;Cubism.&quot;", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
